[{"answer": "I know. I have a sixth sense", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I see dead relationships", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "If I'm going to jump into anything with you, my friend, I need some sign that you're serious about it. About me", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Look, you've gotta admit, you're the most pessimistic person in the world", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Okay. No more jokes. Now. Tell me how you feel", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "About me", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You don't understand, you're not Jewish", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "But the professor probably thinks I am", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Ah, forget about my friend. I don't like it any more than you", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Hey, he was one of my best friends. Now we share a room and he's like a stranger", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ugh, no", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Uh, yeah, we should be back in, uh, many many hours", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Want me to tell you", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Speaking of failed relationships, I was thinking about your Annie Hall theory. Specifically, I was thinking that you're insane", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I said I was joking, so why do you keep bringing it up? 29", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Your attitude's too dour. You've gotta be more fun", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Maybe an omelet", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "So don't get the eggs", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What're you majoring in", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "It was my second question", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "But..", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It's nothing serious, but it is a date", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "We're having dinner tonight. Wanna come", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah, we're definitely broken up. I guess sometimes it seems like we're sliding back into our old patterns", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "And the best part is, it's work study. I think the Psych. department's involved", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "So, uh, got any plans tonight", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Now it's your turn, right", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Fuck. I sure hadn't guessed that", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Since high school, wow", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Uh, I have a friend who says it's because I watch my friend too much", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't even know him. What's so special about this guy, anyway? I mean, are you and he...", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I guess so. You know, we should try to be more exciting. Like the other day, I waited until the last minute before returning a video. And next time, I swear I'm not going to rewind", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Sort of. Well, no, I guess not.  I know something's going on. I'm such a fool. Why are we always attracted to people that are completely wrong for us? Is it because they excite us", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I can be a rebel too. The other day I went to bed without flossing", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Hello? Can I help you", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Hey! Are you my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Sure it is", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No, it isn't", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Um, no, it's just the box. The tape inside is wrestling. 83", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Um, it's been recorded over..", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Why did you", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Really? I'll, I'll have to remember that later. 84", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I wouldn't go that far. She's just a daffy dame, that's all. Now, my friend's foxy, but she's too serious", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What about her", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "But, but... we just saw a movie about how relationships are worth it, no matter what happens. 103", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yeah, I guess we really did", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What was all this, I mean, was any of it 104", "docId": "Burning-Annie.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "But it might lead to... happiness", "qsentId": 48}]